A Finding Aid to the Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries Records, 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969; undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - Ferargil, Inc. - Findlay Galleries, 1917-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5856, Frame 43-142)
    Finch College Museum of Art
    Findlay Art Galleries (Kansas City)
    Findlay Galleries (Chicago)
  - Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego - Fishman, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5856, Frame 143-230)
    Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego
    Fine Arts Institute
    Finger, T. E.
    Arnold Finkel Gallery
    Fire Companies' Adjustment Bureau, Inc.
    Fischer, Sara L.
    Fish, George Winthrop
    Fisher, Carl and Joan
    Franklin Fisher and Associates, Inc.
    Fisher, J. L.
    Fisher, R. G.
    Fishman, Adam
  - Fitch - Floret, 1923-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5856, Frame 231-324)
    Fitch, George H.
    Fitler, Mrs.
    Fitzgerald, Desmond
    Fitzgerald, Harriet
    Five Towns Music and Art Foundation, Inc.
    Flaherty, Leonard E.
    Fleischman, Arthur
    Fleischman, Lawrence A.
    Fleming, William T.
    Flint Institute of Arts
    Floret, Lydia
  - Florida Artist Group, Inc. - Fontaine, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 326-410)
    Florida Artist Group, Inc.
    Florida Gulf Coast Art Center (See also Clearwater Art Museum)
    Florida State College for Women
    Florida State University
    Florie, S. T.
    Flower, E. M.
    Fogarty, Margaret M.
    Fogg Art Museum
    Folinsbee, James
    Folsom, C. M., Jr.
    Fontaine, Joan
  - Forbes Magazine - Frazier, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 411-547)
    Forbes Magazine of Business and Finance
    Forges, Ruth
    Force, Juliana
    Ford Foundation
    Ford, John Hampton
    Ford, William H.
    Forgan, Mrs. Robert R.
    Forman, Joanne
    Fort Dodge Federation of Arts, Inc.
    Fort Wayne Art School and Museum
    Fort Worth Art Association/Fort Worth Art Center
    Fortess, Karl E.
    Fortner, Fred
    Fortune
    Forum Gallery
    Fosdick, J. William
    Foshay, Mrs. W. W.
    Foss, Archibald C.
    Foster and Adams
    Fowler, A. A.
    Fowler, Ethel L.
    Fowler, M. Freelon
    Fox, J. Bertram
    Fox, John Owen
    Pearl Fox Fine Paintings
    Fraad, Daniel
    Fraad, Harriet
    Frames for Collectors
    Francis, George M.
    Frank, Erich P. and Aileen C.
    Frank, Helen
    Frank, J. M.
    Frankel, Cecile R.
    Frankllin, Max
    Fransioli, Thomas A.
    Frantz, Sarah Stanley
    Frazier, John R.
  - Frederick - Fulop, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 548-665)
    Frederick, Rhoda
    Frederickson, F. Lyder
    Women's Guild of the Free Synagogue of Westchester
    Freedman, Harriet D.
    Freer, Charles L.
    Freiman, Ray
    Frelinghuysen, H. O. H.
    French, Daniel Chester
    Frenkel, Robert E.
    Frenkel and Co., Inc.
    Freucl, William C.
    Freudenthal, Mrs. A.
    The Frick Art Reference Library
    Friedlaender, Alex S.
    Friedlander, Herzl
    Friedman, Meyer
    Friend, Weston U.
    Friends of American Art
    Froelich, Paul
    Frondel, Clifford
    Frothingham, John W.
    Fujikawa Gallery
    Fuller, Alvin T.
    Fuller, Justine
    Fuller, Robert H.
    Fulop, Karoly
  - G Contemporary Art/James Goodman Gallery, 1959-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 667-765)
  - Gaffey - Gallery North, 1925-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 766-840)
    Gaffey, Edward R.
    Gage,George
    Gage, William H., Jr.
    Galerie 19
    H. Galka, Inc.
    Gallagher, Edward J., Jr.
    Gallant, Mary Claire
    Gallatin, A. E.
    The Gallery, Inc. (Atlanta)
    The Gallery (Fort Lauderdale)
    Gallery North
  - Gallery of Modern Art including the Huntington Hartford Collection - Gavin, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 841-919)
    Gallery of Modern Art including the Huntington Hartford Collection (See also Hartford, Huntington)
    Gallery-on-the-Hudson
    Gallery Press
    Gallery Reese Palley
    Ganley, Robert David
    Ganz, Sally
    Garber, Daniel
    Garden and Home Builder
    Gardiner, A. P.
    Gardner, Mrs. John L.
    Garelick's Gallery
    Garfield National Bank
    Garrard Publishing Co.
    Garrett, Mrs. George
    Garrett, Mrs. John W.
    Gash, Chester Alan
    Gatch, Elsie Driggs (See Driggs, Elsie)
    Gates, Clinton H.
    Gavin, Ruth Raymond
  - Geddes - Gitlin, 1918-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 920-1035)
    Geddes, D. G.
    Geffen, Felicia
    Gehl, Sidney H.
    Gelber-Epstein Custom Picture Framing
    Gellatly, John
    Genaur, Emily
    Genung, Mrs. C. H.
    George, Thomas
    Georgia Institute of Technology
    H. O. Gerngross and Co., Inc.
    Gessert, Earl
    Gibbes Art Gallery
    Gibbons, Mr. and Mrs. Cedric
    Gibson, Langhorne
    Gibson, Sybil
    Gikow, Ruth
    Gilder, Joseph
    Gilbert, Bill and Sib
    Gilbert, O. Rundle
    Gilbert, Peter
    Gilbert, Regine
    Gilbert, William F.
    Gilchrist, W. A.
    Gilchrist, W. W., Jr.
    Giles, Howard
    Gilkey, Gordon W.
    Gillis, William
    Gimbel, Mrs. Bernard F.
    Gimbel Brothers (See Kende Galleries, Inc.)
    Gitlin, Zachary
  - Glannon - Golden, 1921-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1036-1114)
    Glannon, Edward
    Glasheen, Adeline E.
    Glasheen, Francis
    Glasner, Bertha E.
    Glassford, Pelham David
    Glemby, Mr. and Mrs. Harry
    Glen, Stanley and Ethel B.
    Glidden Buick Corp.
    Glidden, G.
    Glosser, Mrs. Alvin M.
    Gloucester, Mass., City of
    Gloucester Electric Co.
    Gloucester Telephone Co.
    Glover, Jane Louise
    Gloversville Intercultural League
    Gluck, F. J.
    Goddard Gallery
    Godowsky, Frances
    Goldberg, Albert
    Golde, Joseph A.
    Golde, Joseph E.
    Golden Gate International Exposition
    Golden, Richard Davis
  - Goldfarb - Gooch, 1925-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1115-1203)
    Goldfarb, William
    Goldman, Mrs. Albert
    Goldman, Frederick
    Goldman, Mr. and Mrs. Harold J.
    Goldreyer, Daniel
    Goldshlag, Leo J.
    Goldsmith, Morton
    Goldstein, Sanford H.
    Goldstone, Herbert A.
    Golffing, Francis
    Gooch, Mrs. Cecil Milton
  - Good - Gottlieb, 1924-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1204-1276)
    Good, J.
    Good, Robert
    Goodall, Donald B.
    James Goodman Gallery (See G Contemporary Art)
    Goodrich, Lloyd
    Goodsell, Charles W.
    Goodwin, Philip L.
    Goodyear, A. Conger
    Goodyear, George F.
    Gordon, Lois
    Gorman, Bryce
    Gorman, William D.
    Gornoll, Ruth
    Gosline, William A., Jr.
    Dey Gosse Gallery
    Gotcliffe, Sid
    Gotterdam, Paskell
    Gottlieb, Eugene L.
  - Gould - Graham, 1943-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1277-1340)
    Gould, Northram R.
    Gould, Tod
    Grace, Nan
    Grade Teacher
    Grady, James
    Grafly, Dorothy
    Graham, Donald S.
    James Graham and Sons
    Robert C. Graham Gallery
    Graham, Robert MacD., Jr.
  - Grand Central Art Galleries - Grand Street Settlement, 1924-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1341-1424)
    Grand Central Art Galleries
    Grand Central School of Art
    Grand Rapids Art Gallery/Grand Rapids Art Museum
    Grand Street Settlement
  - Granek Frame Schop - Griswold, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1425-1530)
    Granek Frame Shop
    Grant, Earle
    Grassi, Arturo
    Gray-Attwater, Lillian
    Great Neck Cultural Center
    Great Neck Education Association, Inc.
    Greef, Charles B.
    Green, Albert L.
    Greenbaum, Edward S.
    Greenbaum, Sophia
    Greenough, Margaret S.
    Greenville County Museum of Art
    Greenwald, F. L., Jr.
    Greenwich Society of Artists
    Greenwich Village-Gramercy Park Committee of Russia War Relief
    Greenwood, Mrs. Kenneth
    Gregoropoulos, L. John
    A. Grieve Co., Inc.
    Griffin, Howard
    Griffin, Walter
    Griffin, William H.
    Griggs, Mary
    Grinnell Brothers
    Griswold, Mrs. A. W.
  - Grombach - Groves, circa 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5856, Frame 1531-1577)
    Grombach, John V.
    Grosbert, Mr. and Mrs. Hebert L.
    Gross, Earl
    Gross, Sidney
    Gross, Stanley J.
    Grossfield, Sylvia
    Grosso and Co.
    Grosz, George
    Earl Groth and Co.
    Groves, William J.
  - Gruom - Gwyn, circa 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 13-75)
    Gruom, Ed
    Gruppe, Charles P.
    Grusberg, G.
    Guerry, Prosper
    Guertler, Rudolph
    Guest, A. E.
    Guggenheim, Edmond A.
    John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
    Guggenheim, Robert
    Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum
    Guild Hall
    Guild of Boston Artists
    Gummo, Blanchard
    Gump's
    Gurney, Albert R., Jr.
    Gutterdam, P. M.
    Gwyn, Woody
  - Haas - Hambuechen, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 77-167)
    Haas, Clara S.
    Haas, Lillian Henkel
    Habecker, Kent C.
    Hackett, Frances G.
    Haggin Memorial Art Galleries
    Hagimont, Frances
    Hague Art Deliveries, Inc.
    Hahn Brothers Fireproof Warehouses, Inc.
    Hale, J. D.
    Hall, Clifton R.
    Hall, Standish
    Hall, Weeks
    Hallmark Art Award
    Hallowell, Robert
    Halmi, Mrs. Artur
    Halow, A. J.
    Halperin, Theodore P.
    Seymour Halperin Associates
    Halsey, Lilian J.
    Halvorson, Newman T. and Virginia M.
    Hambeuchen, J. W.
    Hambrick, Lucile
  - Hamilton - Harrison, 1929-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 168-311)
    Hamilton, Carl W.
    Hamilton, Chloe
    Hamilton College
    Hamilton, David K.
    Hamlin, Genevieve Karr
    Hamlin, Lucy R.
    Hamlin, Talbot
    Hammerslough, A. J.
    Hammett, Buell
    Hammond, Susan
    Hammond, Roland B.
    Hammond, Ruth
    Hampton Gallery
    Hampton, R. L.
    Hanft, Mr.
    Hanna, Leonard C., Jr.
    Hanna, Ray
    Hans, Edward K.
    Hansel, Mrs.
    Hansen, Einar
    Hansen, H. F.
    Hansen, James L.
    Hanson and Parker
    Hanson, William E.
    Hanzel Galleries, Inc.
    Harding, Agnes Bukley
    Harding, George F.
    Harding, J. M.
    Hardy, DeWitt and Pat
    Hare, Elizabeth Sage
    Hargraves, Rainbolt
    Haring, Victor
    Harkness, Mrs. M.
    Harkness, Mrs. William Hale
    Harline, Catherine
    Arthur H. Harlow and Co.
    Harman, H. G.
    Harner, Lewis H.
    Harnett, Lilian and Joel
    Harper and Brothers
    Marie Harriman Gallery
    Harrington, George B.
    Harris, Edwin A.
    Harrison, Barbara
    Harrison, Birge
    Harrison, Eloise
    Harrison, Justen
    Harrison, Paula
  - Harshe - Hassam, 1918-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 312-395)
    Harshe, William R.
    Hart, Mrs. Louis B.
    Hart, Pop
    Hart Publishing Co.
    Hartford, Huntington (See also Gallery of Modern Art incorporating the Huntington Hartford Collection)
    Hartman, Rosella
    Hartog, Joseph
    Hartwell, S. S.
    Hartwick College
    Harvard Alumni Bulletin
    Harvey, F. Sailor
    Hassam, Childe
  - Haswell - Hawthorne, 1920-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 396-478)
    Haswell, Anthony and Virginia
    Dalzell Hatfield Galleries
    Haug, Frank
    Hawkes, Dr. and Mrs. Forbes
    Hawthorne, Charles
  - Hay - Heitland, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 479-577)
    Hay, John
    Hayden, Richard C.
    Haydock, George S.
    Hayes, Edward
    Hayes, Helen
    Hayes Storage, Packing and Removal Service (See also Cirker's Hayes Storage Warehouse, Inc.)
    Haynes, Caroline C.
    Hayward, Leland
    Haywood, T. Holt
    Hazard, Mrs. Roland
    Heald, Gordon T.
    Heald, J. Nicholas, II
    Healy, A. Augustus
    Hearne, W. L.
    D. C. Heath and Co.
    Heath's Gallery
    Hecht, Ben
    Heckscher Museum
    Hedborg, Mrs.
    Heerman, Norbert
    Hefferman, Marion C.
    Heil, Walter
    Heinzelman, Carl D.
    Heitland, W. Emerton
  - Helbig - Herron, D., 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 578-668)
    Helbig, Henry
    Helck, C. P.
    Held, Louis
    Helen, Inc.
    Helmsley-Spear, Inc.
    Helmsworth, James A.
    Hemphill, Noyes and Co.
    Henderson, P.A.B.
    Henderson, Paul G.
    Henderson, W. Abbott
    Hendrek, Edward
    Heniot, Enrique L.
    Hennessey, James A.
    Henri, Robert
    Henry, David T.
    Henry, Frances L.
    Henry, Mildred H.
    Henry Street Settlement, Armory Show 50th Anniversary Exhibition
    Hepburn, Katharine
    Herbert, Ellen
    Herbert, James D.
    Heritage Gallery
    Herndon, Isabel
    Herrman, E. Adele
    Herron, David
  - John Herron Art Institute/Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana, 1940-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Reel 5857, Frame 669-774)
  - Hervey - Hinchman, 1923-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 776-876)
    Hervey, Wilna and Nan Mason
    Hetzel, Ralph
    Hewitt, Edward Shepard
    H. Heydenryk, Jr. Fine Fames
    Hickey, Florence
    Hidalgo
    High School of Music and Art
    Higgins, Carter C.
    Hillman, Alex L.
    Hillstrom, Richard L.
    Hinchman, Anne
    Hinchman, Margaretta S.
  - Hirsch - Hoftrup, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 877-949)
    Hirsch, Barbara M.
    Hirsch, Joseph
    Hirschl and Adler Galleries, Inc.
    Hirschland, F.H.
    Hirshhorn, Joseph H./Joseph H. Hirshhorn Collection (See also Lerner, Abram)
    Hirst, Claude Raguet
    Hirst, Donald
    Hite, Marcia S./Allen R. Hite Art Institute, University of Louisville
    Hitzler, Florence
    Hixen
    Hoagland, Ruth H.
    Hochschild, Mrs. Harold
    Hodson, E. L.
    Hoerman, Mrs. Kirk
    Hofield, Irene
    Hoffman, Mrs. Lewis
    Hofmann, Earl Francis
    Hofstra College/Hofstra University
    Hoftrup, J. Lars
  - Holabird and Root and Burgee - Hopkinson, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 950-1085)
    Holabird and Root and Burgee
    Holbrook, Alfred H.
    Holbrook, Hollis
    Holden, Eleanor
    Holland Galleries
    Hollander and Bernheimer (See also Bernheimer and Zucker)
    Hollins College
    Hollins, Elizabeth and Jay
    Hollister, Ruth A.
    Holmehill, Inc.
    Holmes, George
    Holmquist, Ibbie
    Holston, Bill
    Holt, Rhinehart and Winston, Inc.
    Holyoke Museum of Natural History and Art
    Honolulu Academy of Arts
    Hood, David R.
    Hoover, Bee
    Hoover, Clare
    Constance Hope Associates, Inc.
    Hope, Henry and Sally
    Hopkins Center Art Gallery (See Dartmouth College)
    Hopkins, Florence O.
    Hopkinson, Charles
  - Hopper, Edward and Jo, 1924-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 1086-1338)
  - Hopper Estate - Hubbard, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 1340-1455)
    Hopper Estate
    Horch, L. L.
    Horelick, Jules
    Horizon
    Horley, Lester
    Grace Horne Gallery
    Horten, Mrs. B. F.
    Horter, Elizabeth Lentz (Mrs. Earl)
    Horton Galleries
    Horton, Harry V.
    Hoskins, Beatrice T.
    Hosmer, Billy Price
    Hostetler, Mrs. Joseph C.
    Hotel Alcadel
    Hotel Publications, Inc.
    Houff, Frances M.
    Houghton Mifflin Co.
    Housatonic Valley Conference
    House Beautiful Magazine
    Howard, Arthur P.
    Howard, Jane Berlandina
    Howard, Lee
    Howard University
    Howe, E. Ruth
    Howell, Mrs. Charles A.
    Howland, Isabella
    Hoyle, Charles A.
    Hoyte, Charles B.
    Hubbard, Earl Wade and Barbara
  - Hudnut - Hyperion, 1919-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5857, Frame 1456-1580)
    Hudnut, Alex
    Hudson Guild, Inc.
    J. L. Hudson Co.
    Hudson Shipping Co.
    Huf, Mrs. W. L.
    Hult, Bernard
    Humphries, J. C.
    Humphrey, Eleanor B.
    Hunnewell, Mrs. Hollis
    Hunt, Mrs. A.
    Hunt, Grace
    Hunt, Rachel Miller
    Hunter College
    George Thomas Hunter Gallery of Art (See Chattanooga Art Association)
    Hunterdon County Art Center
    Hunting, Mary I. and David D.
    Huntington, Christopher
    Huntington, John W.
    Huntington, Robert W.
    Hurd, Hiram H.
    Hurry, Lucy W.
    Hurtt, Mr. and Mrs. Clyde B.
    Hurwitz, Leo
    Hutchins, Robert
    Hutzler, Elsa
    Hyde, Mrs. Louis F./Mrs. Louis F. Hyde Collection
    Hydeman, Albert L.
    Hyder, Inez
    Hynd, Fred S.
    Hyperion Press
  - Hyslop, F. E., Jr., circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 12-15)
  - Iglehart - Ingraham, 1927-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 17-137)
    Iglehart, Wendy
    Ingersoll, Anna W.
    Ingersoll, R. Sturgis
    Ingraham, David
  - Inn at Buck Hills Falls - Jacobsson, 1918-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 138-272)
    Inn at Buck Hills Falls
    Institute of Contemporary Arts
    Institute of Modern Art/Institute of Contemporary Art
    Institute for Research
    Instructor
    Insular Arts Council
    Internal Revenue
    International Appliance Co.
    International Business Machines Corp. (IBM)
    International Directory of Arts
    International Festival of Art (See United Nations Tribute and International Festival of Art)
    International Monetary Fund
    Inter-State Detective Agency
    Iowa State College
    Iowa Union and School of Fine Arts
    Irwin, Gerda M.
    Iselin, Mr. and Mrs. Herbert M.
    Isham, Mr. and Mrs. Lincoln
    Isidor, J. S.
    Israel Museum (Mrs. T. J. Israel)
    Israel, Laura N.
    Ed Iverson Trucking
    Jacks, N. B.
    Jackson, David P.
    Jackson, Martha K.
    Jackson, Roscoe B.
    Jacobs, Mrs. S. Allen
    Jacobs, Bernard
    Jacobs, John H.
    Jacobs, Philip F.
    Jacobs, Wilma
    Jacobsen, Mrs. Hugh Newell
    Jacobsson, Edward Gustave
  - James, Alexander and Frederika, 1941-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 273-429)
  - James, M. - Jenkins, 1922-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 430-522)
    James, Mickey
    James, Oliver B.
    Jameson, Mrs. P. M.
    Jamison Galleries
    Janns, Anne Marie
    January, A. M.
    Jaques, Gertrude M.
    Jarman, Sally Long
    Jefferson, Blanche
    Jefferson Gallery
    Jeffries, John
    Jelleff, Frank R.
    Jellineck, Rena F.
    Jenkins, A. W.
    Jenkins, Esther E.
    Jenkins, J. E.
  - Jennings and Cleaves, Inc., 1920-1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 523-638)
  - Jennings, Mrs. B. - Joint Board Fur Dressers' and Dyers' Unions, 1923-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 639-720)
    Jennings, Mrs. Brewster
    Jennings, G.
    Jesup and Lamont
    Jewell, Edward Alden
    Jewish Frontier
    Jewish Memorial Hospital
    Jewish Museum
    Jewish Theological Seminary of American
    Johansson, Alison C.
    Johnsen, David
    Johnsen, May
    Johnson, A. L.
    Johnson, Albert R.
    Johnson, Alice
    Johnson, Benjamin Franklin
    Chester H. Johnson Galleries
    Johnson, Mrs. Frederick
    Johnson, Helena Chase
    Johnson-Humrickhouse Memorial Museum
    Johnson, L.
    Johnson, Leonard Williams
    Johnson, Philip
    Johnson, Robert A.
    Johnson, Robert Underwood
    Johnson, William J.
    Joint Board Fur Dressers' and Dyers' Union
  - Jones - Kamperman, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 721-802)
    Jones, Alfred E., Jr.
    Jones, Mrs. Alfred Winslow
    Jones, Arthur W.
    Jones, B. H.
    Jones, Mrs. Herbert
    Jones, W. B.
    Jones Art Galleries, Inc.
    Jonson, Raymond
    Joske's of Texas
    Joslyn Memorial/Joslyn Art Museum
    Joyner, J. Brooks
    Judson, Mrs. Clay
    Judson, Harold
    Junior Art Gallery, Inc.
    Junior League of Jackson
    Juster Gallery
    Kachurin
    Kaese's Lakeview Farm
    Kahn, Laurence S.
    Kalamazoo College
    Kalamazoo Institute of Arts
    Kamperman, George
  - Kander - Kansas State College/Kansas State University, 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 803-902)
    Kander, Allen
    Kanin, Garson
    Kansas City Art Institute and School of Design
    Kansas City Museum
    Kansas City Southern Industries, Inc.
    Kansas State College/Kansas State University
  - Kantor - Katzieff, 1926-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 903-997)
    Kantor, Morris
    Kaplan, Alice M.
    Kaplan, Morton
    Kaplan, Richard
    Karfiol, Bernard
    Arthur C. Karlin Co., Inc.
    Tirca Karlis Gallery
    Karnes, Marilyn
    Karten, Lawrence B.
    Katonah Gallery, Inc.
    Katz, Joseph
    Katzenbach and Warren, Inc.
    Katzieff, J. D.
  - Kauffman - Kehoe, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 998-1123)
    Kauffmann, Milton
    Kaufman, Irving
    Kaufmann, Edgar, Jr.
    Kay, David
    Kaye, L. B.
    Keane, William L.
    Keaney, John
    W. R. Keating and Co.
    Keck, Andrew S.
    Keefe, John W.
    Keeler, Rollston
    Kehoe, M.
  - Keighley - Kennedy, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 1124-1210)
    Keighley, William and Genevieve
    Keith, Lucile
    Kelley, Mrs.
    Kelley, Chapman
    Kelle, F. B.
    Kellogg, George A.
    Kellogg, Jean
    Kelly, Miss
    Kelly, Evelyn
    Kelly, John
    Kelly, Leon
    Kem, Mrs. James P.
    Kemp, Louis F.
    Kemper, William T., Jr.
    Kendall, Messmore
    Kende Galleries, Inc.
    Kennard, J.
    Kennedy and Co./Kennedy Galleries, Inc.
    Kennedy, David O'D.
    Kennedy, Mrs. Gilbert
    Kennedy, J. M.
    Kennedy, John F., Pres. Elect and Mrs.
    Kennedy, Joe
    Kennedy, William H.
  - Kenreich - Kimball, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 1211-1327)
    Kenreich, Virginia B.
    Kent Grand Central Garage
    Kent, Norman
    Kent, Rockwell
    Kenyon College
    Frederick Keppell and Co., Inc.
    Kerr, Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin Fisher
    Khahn, Rhoda S.
    Kibbee, Mrs. Henry Myers
    Kierstead, Wilson H., Jr.
    Kieswetter, Dayton T.
    Kildea, Mrs. York
    Kiln Club
    Kimball, David C.
    Kimball, Yeffee V.
  - Kindler - Klitgaard, 1924-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 5858, Frame 1328-1474)
    Kindler, Alice
    King, Gwyneth
    King, Lawrence
    King, Paul
    King, Ralph T.
    King, William V.
    Kingdon, Frank
    Kingsport Press Sales Agency
    Kinney, William S.
    Kinney System Rent a Car
    Kiorboe, Mr. and Mrs. Vilhelm
    Kipbuth, De Laney
    Kirkham and Hall
    Kirsch, John
    Kit Kat Club
    Klatt, C.
    Kleege, James H.
    Kleeman Galleries
    Klitgaard, Georgina
    Klitgaard, Kaj
  - Knapp - Kozlow, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Reel 5858, Frame 1476-1596)
    Knapp, Sally Hazard
    Knappen, James F.
    Knauth, Oswald
    Knight, Alice V.
    Knight, E. F.
    Knight, Frederic
    M. Knoedler and Co., Inc.
    Knoepke, Olga H.
    Knopf, Otto
    Knowlton, Hugh
    Kogod, Robert P.
    Kohn, Bernard A.
    Kohnstamm, M. Jacques
    Kolbe, Eugene
    Komroff, Elinor Barnard
    Samuel M. Kootz Gallery, Inc.
    Koren, Harriet
    Kormendi, Laszlo
    Kornblum, Irving
    Korner and Wood Co.
    Kornfeld, Arnold
    Koven, Mrs. Gustav
    Kosicki, Witold Watha
    Kottler, Ronald
    Kouwenhoven, Alexandra and William G.
    Kozlow, Richard
  - Kraus - Lake, 1921-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 13-134)
    Kraus, Eleanor
    C. W. Kraushaar Art Galleries/Kraushaar Galleries
    Kreindler, Doris Barsky
    Kress, Edith D. S.
    Kriegler, Joseph
    Kristiansen, Georgina
    Kroll, Leon
    Kronberg, Dr. and Mrs. Bernard
    Kronberg, Louis
    Kruik, Arie B.
    Kuehne, Max
    Kulicke, Barbara and Bob
    Kulicke Frames, Inc.
    Kupferman, Joseph
    Kurson, Phyllis
    Kurtz, Olga
    La Boiteux, Mrs. M. H.
    La Branch, George
    Lacey, J. Stewart
    Ladies' Home Journal
    Laguna Beach Art Association
    Lahey, Dick
    La Hotan, Robert
    Lake, Frederick
  - Lamb - Lathrop, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 135-244)
    Lamb, John A.